Tufts Daily Records UA176
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1980 -- 2009; UA176.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 556 Digital Object(s) Of 556 digital objects, 495 have extent information comprising 11,866 files.; 47.35 Gigabytes Of 555 digital objects, 495 have extent information comprising 47.35 GB.
  - Daily Dinner and Spring Fling, 2005; UA176.004948; 597.84 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 248 files.
  - Exposure exhibition: Vanishing, 2005; UA176.004949; 288 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 26 files.
  - Men's basketball and track, 2005; UA176.004950; 353.01 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 145 files.
    - Men's basketball, 2005; UA176.004951; 163.5 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 68 files.
    - Men's track, 2005; UA176.004952; 189.51 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 77 files.
  - Men's varsity soccer versus MIT, 2005; UA176.004953; 107.4 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 67 files.
  - Men's soccer, football, and homecoming, 2005; UA176.004954; 399.17 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 278 files.
  - Pep Rally and Athletic Department awards, 2005; UA176.004955; 360.88 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 195 files.
  - Sports, Monster, and Somerville Theater Sci Fi Festival, 2005; UA176.004956; 694.49 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 250 files.
    - Hockey, 2005 February 11; UA176.004957; 387.07 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 131 files.
    - Men's basketball, 2005 February 12; UA176.004958; 147.74 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 58 files.
    - Monster, 2005; UA176.004959; 133.87 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 49 files.
    - Somerville Theater Sci Fi Festival, 2005; UA176.004960; 25.81 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 12 files.
  - Swimming versus Trinity, 2005; UA176.004961; 211.44 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 153 files.
  - Women's lacrosse versus Wellesley, 2005; UA176.004962; 637.13 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 188 files.
  - Student performance and art gallery, 2005; UA176.004963; 311.99 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 148 files.
  - Winter Bash, 2005; UA176.004964; 5.23 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 13 files.
  - Women's lacrosse, 2005; UA176.004965; 143.68 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 45 files.
  - Men's and women's basketball, 2005 --2006; UA176.004966; 20.97 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
  - Sports, 2005 --2006; UA176.004967; 82.11 Megabytes; 2 Digital Object(s) 2 digital objects comprising 53 files.
    - Soccer Dinner photographs, 2005; UA176.004968; 38.77 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 26 files.
  - Men's basketball versus Williams, 2006 January 20; UA176.004969; 126.56 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 88 files.
  - Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship Politics of Fear symposium, 2006 January 23; UA176.004970; 191.53 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 84 files.
  - Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship keynote speaker, 2006 January 24; UA176.004971; 124.55 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 54 files.
  - Boryana "Bory" Damyanova memorial service, 2006 January 25; UA176.004972; 152.61 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 62 files.
  - Men's basketball, 2006 January; UA176.004973; 569.89 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 308 files.
    - Men's basketball versus Connecticut College, 2006 January 27; UA176.004974; 226.33 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 148 files.
    - Men's basketball versus Wesleyan, 2006 January 28; UA176.004975; 343.56 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 160 files.
  - Hockey versus Wesleyan, 2006 February 02; UA176.004976; 221.85 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 160 files.
  - Indoor track, 2006 February 04; UA176.004977; 212.19 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 140 files.
  - Men's basketball versus Bates, 2006 February 04; UA176.004978; 129.67 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 93 files.
  - Fencing, 2006 February 11; UA176.004979; 310.01 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 186 files.
  - Women's basketball versus Amherst, 2006 February 11; UA176.004980; 223.96 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 141 files.
  - Hockey versus Babson, 2006 February 12; UA176.004981; 395 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 125 files.
  - Men's basketball versus Williams, 2006 February 18; UA176.004982; 251.85 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 171 files.
  - Women's lacrosse versus Babson, 2006 April 13; UA176.004983; 269.2 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 106 files.
  - Sigma Nu Sausagefest, 2006 April; UA176.004984; 76.22 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 27 files.
  - Soccer, 2006 September 09; UA176.004985; 502.59 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 168 files.
    - Men's soccer, 2006 September 09; UA176.004986; 402.44 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 132 files.
    - Women's soccer, 2006 September 09; UA176.004987; 100.15 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 36 files.
  - Men's football and women's soccer, 2006 September; UA176.004988; 4.64 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 80 files.
    - Men's football versus Hamilton, 2006 September 23; UA176.004989; 1.4 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 26 files.
    - Women's soccer and football versus Bates (Homecoming), 2006 September 30; UA176.004990; 3.24 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 54 files.
  - Field hockey, 2006 September -- 2006 October; UA176.004991; 170.24 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 46 files.
    - Field hockey versus Wellesley, 2006 September 13; UA176.004992; 79.61 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 22 files.
    - Field hockey versus Wesleyan, 2006 October 17; UA176.004993; 90.62 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 24 files.
  - Sailing practice, Spring 2006; UA176.004994; 67.09 Megabytes; 18 Digital Object(s) 18 digital objects comprising 77 files.
    - Aaron Gerratt and Meredith Pickett, Spring 2006; UA176.004995; 1.28 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
    - Alex Singer and Zoe Bolesta, Spring 2006; UA176.004996; 823.01 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
    - Dan Altreuter and Mika Green, Spring 2006; UA176.004997; 4.73 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
    - Dave Siegal and Anna Martin, Spring 2006; UA176.004998; 2.73 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Doug Randall and Vanessa Weekley, Spring 2006; UA176.004999; 1005.64 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
    - Emily Randall and Doug Randall, Spring 2006; UA176.005000; 2.58 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Gretchen Curtis and Jen Giroux, Spring 2006; UA176.005001; 6 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
    - Ian Beam and Liz Phelps, Spring 2006; UA176.005002; 2.6 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Jack Wittpenn and Laura Fong, Spring 2006; UA176.005003; 5.99 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
    - Jason Majane and Ian Oppenheim, Spring 2006; UA176.005004; 5.19 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
    - Jeff Cruise and Chyrssa Rask, Spring 2006; UA176.005005; 6.46 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
    - Kaity Storck and Lyndsay Gibbons Neff, Spring 2006; UA176.005006; 7.71 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 9 files.
    - Michael Hodess and Megan Peal, Spring 2006; UA176.005007; 2.74 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Peter Fallon and Meredith Groff, Spring 2006; UA176.005008; 1.67 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - Sam Adelman and Alex Lavers, Spring 2006; UA176.005009; 3.69 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - Stephen Cox and Catherin Shelley, Spring 2006; UA176.005010; 3.23 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - Zander Kirkland and Katie Greenlee, Spring 2006; UA176.005011; 8.71 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - Copley Square and Boston Public Library, 2006; UA176.005012; 182.19 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 50 files.
  - Flowering trees, 2006; UA176.005013; 52.73 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
  - Lacrosse, tennis, and sports previews, 2006; UA176.005014; 173.32 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 123 files.
    - Men's lacrosse, 2006; UA176.005015; 21.86 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 15 files.
    - Men's tennis, 2006; UA176.005016; 45.36 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 33 files.
    - Sports previews, 2006; UA176.005017; 38.83 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 27 files.
    - Women's lacrosse, 2006; UA176.005018; 67.28 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 48 files.
  - Men's hockey, 2006; UA176.005019; 124.51 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 41 files.
  - Men's lacrosse and Sri Lanka lecture, 2006; UA176.005020; 175.75 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 125 files.
  - Men's soccer, 2006; UA176.005021; 4.69 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 95 files.
    - Men's soccer, 2006; UA176.005022; 1.56 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 30 files.
    - Men's soccer versus Salve Regina, 2006; UA176.005023; 609.19 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
    - Men's soccer versus Wesleyan, 2006; UA176.005024; 1.5 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 25 files.
    - Men's soccer versus Portsmouth, 2006; UA176.005025; 1.03 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 26 files.
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 2006; UA176.005026; 29.35 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 19 files.
  - Women's soccer, 2006; UA176.005027; 7.07 Megabytes; 4 Digital Object(s) 4 digital objects comprising 129 files.
    - Women's soccer versus Worcester, 2006; UA176.005028; 2.23 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 44 files.
    - Women's soccer versus Bates, Homecoming, 2006; UA176.005029; 1.66 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 32 files.
    - Women's soccer versus Wesleyan, 2006; UA176.005030; 3.17 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 53 files.
  - Zeta Psi rush, 2006; UA176.005031; 156.89 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 110 files.
  - Fall Ball photo spread, 2007; UA176.005032; 55 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 29 files.
  - Cross country, 2008; UA176.005033; 401.27 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 84 files.
    - Men's cross country, 2008; UA176.005034; 165.27 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 35 files.
    - Women's cross country, 2008; UA176.005035; 236 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 49 files.
  - Tattoo convention, 2008 September 13; UA176.005036; 129.54 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 37 files.
  - Swimming, 2009 November 20; UA176.005037; 626.53 Megabytes; 12 Digital Object(s) 12 digital objects comprising 51 files.
    - Andrew Vidikan, 2009 November 20; UA176.005038; 72.09 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
    - Branden Ching, 2009 November 20; UA176.005039; 46.33 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - Erin Nicole, 2009 November 20; UA176.005040; 54.13 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - J. Becket Linn, 2009 November 20; UA176.005041; 65.3 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
    - Jon Cohn, 2009 November 20; UA176.005042; 26.84 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - Kroetch, 2009 November 20; UA176.005043; 59.39 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
    - Krommel, I think, 2009 November 20; UA176.005044; 31.36 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Lauren Quan, 2009 November 20; UA176.005045; 12.85 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
    - Lindsay York, 2009 November 20; UA176.005046; 34.58 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Max Salzberg, 2009 November 20; UA176.005047; 40.7 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - Ryan Marko, 2009 November 20; UA176.005048; 93.02 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
- Negatives, 1905 -- 2004; 1980 -- 2004; UA176.002; 5.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains negatives produced by the Tufts Daily between 1980 and 2004. Series may include information sheets for the negatives, contact sheets, and Tufts Daily office documentation.
  Negatives are arranged chronologically by semester or academic year. Each folder contains negatives from one binder. Binders were generally labeled and dated and that information was retained. Undated binders were placed at the end of the series based on apparent dates. When dating individual negative sheets, the date on negative sheet took precedence over binder label. Descriptive titles [] replaced non-descriptive binder titles, such as "Requisitions" and "Negative to be picked up by", and were added to un-labeled binders. The original, non-descriptive titles appear in the Notes field. Subjects include news, events, sports, feature stories, students, faculty, and campus facilities.
  This series is arranged chronologically by semester or academic year.
  - All Categories, Fall, 1983 -- 1984; UA176.002.003.00001
    - Homecoming Parade, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00001; Kasch, Ed (Box 3)
    - Football, 1983; UA176.002.003.00001.00002; Birger, Stu (Box 3)
    - Soccer and Tennis, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00003; Ostberg, P. (Box 3)
    - Women's Basketball and Track, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00004; Stevens, N. (Box 3)
    - Women's Basketball and Men's Track, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00005; Stevens, N. (Box 3)
    - Concert, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00006 (Box 3)
    - Soccer, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00007 (Box 3)
    - Women's Soccer and Field Hockey, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00008; Matt- Gary (Box 3)
    - Peace in Lebanon Seminar, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00009 (Box 3)
    - Lacrosse, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00010 (Box 3)
    - Basketball vs. Nicaragua (Exhib.), 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00011 (Box 3)
    - Faculty Meeting: Campus Center Construction, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00012; Haas, Tim (Box 3)
    - Matriculation, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00013 (Box 3)
    - Fire At Cousens, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00014 (Box 3)
    - Homecoming, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00015; Shelman (Box 3)
    - Park Obstacle and Campus Center, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00016 (Box 3)
    - Bubs, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00017 (Box 3)
    - Jean Mayer- Fireside Chat: Ex- College Anniversary Bulletin Board, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00018 (Box 3)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00019 (Box 3)
    - Volleyball, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00020 (Box 3)
    - Lacrosse: Soccer, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00021 (Box 3)
    - The Jumbo/Phil. Lecture, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00022; Adderly, C (Box 3)
    - CSL: Congressman's Lecture, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00023; Adderley, C (Box 3)
    - Faculty. Meeting, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00024; Oillon, Jeanne; Adderley, C.;Curtis, Grant; Birger, S. (Box 3)
    - Deputy Prime Minister Malaysia, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00025 (Box 3)
    - Women's Week- Lecture, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00026 (Box 3)
    - Hockey, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00027 (Box 3)
    - Jean Mayer Hunger Lecture: Prof. Teichman/ Lavrent, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00028; Adderley, Catherine (Box 3)
    - Voting Booth: Mr. William B. Dale T '47 The Role of The IMF in Int'l Negotiations, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00029; Adderley,Catherine (Box 3)
    - Women's Basketball: Track and Field, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00030; Carole (Box 3)
    - Dorm Debate- Cabot: MDA Hospital Bed Race, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00031; Magowen, Torres Winner (Box 3)
    - Nuclear Weapons Forum: Around Somerville, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00032; Carole (Box 3)
    - Father Mondale: Ex Coll Flag, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00033 (Box 3)
    - Macphie, Campus Center Construction, Students in Braker Hall, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00034 (Box 3)
    - Unidentified Man, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00035 (Box 3)
    - Rally, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00036; Cathy (Box 3)
    - Editor's Party/ Marriot, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00037 (Box 3)
    - Unknown Prof., 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00038 (Box 3)
    - Soccer, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00039 (Box 3)
    - Soccer, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00040; Ostburg, Peter (Box 3)
    - Men's Soccer, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00041; Saferstein, Jon (Box 3)
    - Indian Ambassador: Computer Fair- Eaton, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00042; Adderley, Catherine (Box 3)
    - Homecoming 84, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00043; Gary (Box 3)
    - Homecoming Parade: filed Hockey, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00044; Nathaniel (Box 3)
    - King- Queen Candidates, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00045 (Box 3)
    - Sol Gittleman: LSL Meeting, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00046; Haas, Tim (Box 3)
    - Parent's Weekend, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00047; Haas, Tim (Box 3)
    - Speaking For Mondale Campaign, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00048; Kasch, Ed (Box 3)
    - Unidentified Man, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00049 (Box 3)
    - Lecture: Perils of Protectionism: Rugby: Tufts vs. Wesleyan, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00050; Adderley, Catherine (Box 3)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00051; Stu (Box 3)
    - Pente and Campus Center, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00052 (Box 3)
    - Men's Soccer and Rugby, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00053; Silverstein, Jon (Box 3)
    - Volleyball and Soccer, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00054 (Box 3)
    - Women's Soccer, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00055; Saferstein, Jon (Box 3)
    - Soccer, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00056 (Box 3)
    - Stuff, 1984; UA176.002.003.00001.00057 (Box 3)
  - News and Features, Fall, 1984 -- 1986; UA176.002.003.00002
    Includes: Protests/rallies/events; lectures; music groups; celebrities; plays; students; scenes of campus; buildings.
    - Faculty Mtg./ Food Fair, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00001 (Box 3)
    - Out Front Party, 1984 -- 1986; UA176.002.003.00002.00002; Nathaniel (Box 3)
    - Accident at Houston Hall, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00003; Carole (Box 3)
    - Black Comedy Play, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00004; Birgen, Stu (Box 3)
    - Student Leadership Conf., 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00005; Gornel, Yusuf (Box 3)
    - Student Senate, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00006; Adderley, Catherine (Box 3)
    - Lunch Line: W. Germany Peace Lecture, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00007; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
    - TCU Senate(PIRG Debate): Politics, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00008; Adderley, Catherine; Deschapelles, Mike (Box 3)
    - TCU Senate Mtg.: Dean Colcord, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00009; Adderley, Catherine (Box 3)
    - Economics of T.V./ Oxfam Snack Bar, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00010; Haas, Tim (Box 3)
    - Bolivian Music, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00011; Carole (Box 3)
    - Dreams Lecture: Mel King, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00012; Stevens, Nathaniel (Box 3)
    - Massachusetts Senators, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00013; Birgar, Stu (Box 3)
    - Lecture- KAL Tragedy, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00014; Adderley, Catherine (Box 3)
    - National Condom Week, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00015; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
    - El Salvador Lecture, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00016; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
    - Controversial Speaker Forum, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00017; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
    - Students, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00018 (Box 3)
    - Random people, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00019 (Box 3)
    - Library, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00020; Levenson, Carole (Box 3)
    - Students, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00021 (Box 3)
    - Students: Football, 1984; UA176.002.003.00002.00022; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
  - President Jean Mayer, faculty, staff, Fall, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003
    - Pres. Jean Mayer and Sports, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00001; Kasch, Ed (Box 3)
    - Deans Maxwell, Murphy and Reitman/Italian Club Ice Cream, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00002; Kasch, Ed (Box 3)
    - New Chaplin, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00003; Birgen, Stu (Box 3)
    - Jack Dunn, Inst. Planning, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00004; Adderley, Catherine (Box 3)
    - Deans Colcord, Murphy, Reitman, Knable, Flaherty, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00005; Stevens, Nathaniel; Adderley, Catherine (Box 3)
    - Bill Eastwood, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00006; Putnam, Connie (Box 3)
    - Fr. Michael Hunt, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00007; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
    - Charles LeBlanc, April Fools, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00008; Rietman (Box 3)
    - Prof. Robert Elias Lecture: Track Javelin Thrower Dick Nidley, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00009; Haas, Tim (Box 3)
    - Pres. Jean Mayer, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00010; Weiss, Dana (Box 3)
    - Jean Mayer and TCU Senate Mtg., 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00011; Adderley, Catherine (Box 3)
    - Dr. Hormats, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00012; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
    - Prof. Teichman and Kathy Baker, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00013; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
    - Deans Moffatt, Knable, Colcord, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00014; Kasch, Ed (Box 3)
    - Elaine Bunn, Dean Shane, Rabbi Summit, Fr. Hunt, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00015; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
    - Faculty and Tufts Trip, 1984; UA176.002.003.00003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Sports, Fall, 1984; UA176.002.003.00004
    - Basketball (Men's), 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00001; Stevens, Nathaniel (Box 3)
    - Basketball, 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00002; Deschapelles, Michael (Box 3)
    - Field Hockey (Women's), 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00003; Alex (Box 3)
    - Football (Men), 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00004; Levenson, Carole (Box 3)
    - Football, Lincoln Scenery, 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00005; Carole (Box 3)
    - Rugby/Lecture, 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00006; Kasch, Ed (Box 3)
    - Rugby (Women's), 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00007; Peter (Box 3)
    - Soccer (Women's) Varsity, 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00008; Birgen, Stu (Box 3)
    - Soccer (Women's), 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00009; Levenson, Carole (Box 3)
    - Soccer (Women's) vs. Williams, 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00010; Stevens, Nathaniel (Box 3)
    - Soccer (Women's), 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00011; M., Alex (Box 3)
    - Tennis (Women's), 1984; UA176.002.003.00004.00012; MacGregor, Alex (Box 3)